Welcome to Mariners Church. I'm so glad
that you are with us today. I want to
welcome those watching online. I want to
welcome those who are with a group of
people for Mariners hosted here. If you
have a minute, my name is Eric. I'm the
senior pastor here at Mariners. And I
want to celebrate two things before I
jump into our study. First, last week
across all of our congregations
including Mariners online was really
special. We had a rooted celebration and
many of you took rooted online with a
rooted group and then at the celebration
we invited people to place their faith
in Jesus and 173 people last week
confessed faith in Christ. So beautiful.
And then we had baptisms as well. We had
saw 270 people get baptized across all
our congregations throughout Southern
California. So last weekend was a major
celebration. I'm really thankful for you
who are generous to your church. It's
through your generosity that all of
these great things from a human
perspective are happening because God
uses your generosity to build his his
church and so thank you for being a
part. And I also want to say happy
Father's Day to all the dads. I am so
proud of you men for being a man who
follows after God because following
after him you then are the kind of man
that causes your family to flourish,
that your business, your place where you
work, that other people are blessed
because you are a man who is being
formed into the image of Jesus, becoming
more and more like him. And I know that
you know the best way for me to honor
you as a dad, as a father this weekend
is to teach the scripture to you because
that's how we grow as men by throwing
ourselves into the word. Now that's not
not true for dads and for men, but for
all of us and so we're going to continue
in our teaching series this weekend in
the book of Numbers.
For many years I was the young leader.
And then I'm not the young leader
anymore. You know, you're young and then
all of a sudden you're not the young
leader anymore. And in the middle I
started when millennials entered the
workforce I was one who believed in the
next generation because people have
always been believed in me or they gave
me a shot when I was a young leader and
so I gave many others a shot and
invested in millennials at both in
ministry and in the marketplace. And
then I noticed as I would get close to
that generation, the generation right
beneath me, I'm I'm Gen X, that they
would sometimes make fun of me in a
loving way, but when they got
comfortable around me, they would poke
fun at at things that millennials would
poke fun at Gen X for. They would say
our jeans were too baggy or that we
overemphasized how tough we were because
we rode in the back of a station wagon
without a seatbelt. Um they they would
make fun of me when I would call and
leave a voicemail like that was breaking
some kind of cardinal rule like you
should never leave a voicemail at all.
And so millennials would kind of make
fun of me and other leaders in my
generation. And then in recent years,
it's been fascinating and a little bit
enjoyable to watch Gen Z enter into the
workforce and Gen Z start to poke fun at
millennials. It's like the cool kids who
made fun of me getting made fun of is
really fascinating to see that that Gen
Z will then make fun of millennials for
how tight their pants are. I was made
fun of my pants for too baggy. Gen Z
makes fun of millennials for for having
too tight of pants, which I kind of
agree with to be honest with you, if
you're a dude you can't put your wallet
in your back pocket then your pants are
too tight. They would make fun of them
for some of the language that they would
use like adulting and iconic, lol. I
mean terms like that that Gen Z would
would call millennials uncs and so it's
not a good term. It means like uncle
like you're too old. And it's just been
fascinating to watch. Now sociologists
say that is very normal that every
generation rebels a bit against the
generation before them. That there's
something inside of us that wants to
rebel.
We actually root for rebels. I've seen
this in my own life when I will watch a
movie or a television show. I can I can
start rooting for the bad guys. When the
the the show Prison Break came out came
my wife for one Father's Day got me like
a massive DVD set of Prison Break and we
would binge watch it and I found myself
rooting for the people to break out of
prison. Now, some of them were wrongly
there but not all of them were wrongly
there and I was rooting for all of them
to get out of prison. Rooting for the
mafia family in a mafia show. Rooting
for Billy Kid in a western. Rooting for
the bad guys, for the rebels. What's in
us that is attracted to the rebel a bit.
And I've noticed this even spills out in
real life, not just movies and shows.
May of last year, 10 inmates escaped
from a prison in New Orleans where I
grew up and they escaped through a a
wall where they had taken a toilet out
and they wrote on the wall as they were
escaping, "This was too easy. LOL."
Essentially, they were evidently
millennial inmates. And so, they escaped
through the hole in the wall and they
were on the run. I found myself I I
maybe I shouldn't confess this rooting
for them. Just wondering, will they be
able to escape? Will they be able to get
a new identity? Will they be Will they
get a fresh start? Everybody wants a
fresh start. I hope that they get a
fresh start. And then I started watching
them online like seeing where they were,
how many were getting captured, if they
were still out um if they had not yet
been arrested again.
And I realized that the people I were
rooting for are people who should not be
out on the streets. Murderers and
attempted murderers. Like, what is wrong
with me that I'm rooting for these
rebels? The reality is for all of us
there is something inside of us that is
going to rebel.
And I'm going to challenge you this
weekend in this teaching to rebel in the
right direction.
If it's true, and I believe that it is,
that all of us worship something or
someone, that we give our affection to
something or someone. If all of us are
worshippers, that means then we're also
all of us are rebels.
What we worship, we will then rebel in
the opposite direction. We will rebel
against the opposite thing of what it is
that we worship. So, I'm going to
challenge you to take this rebellion
that all of us have within us and
channel it in the right direction. We're
going to look at a famous rebellion in
scripture today in the book of Numbers.
We've been walking through this
incredible book in the Bible, the book
of Numbers. This is God's people in the
wilderness for 40 years. They have been
rescued from Egyptian slavery, that's
the book of Exodus. They're going to go
into the promised land that God has for
them, that's the book of Joshua. In
between is the book of Numbers. They're
in the wilderness. We saw last week that
God told the first generation that were
in the wilderness because you constantly
complain and grumble and you keep
telling me you don't want me and you
wish you were back in slavery, then
fine. You're not going to enter into the
promised land. The whole first
generation, except for Joshua and Caleb,
they're all going to die in the
wilderness. And we'll see as we continue
through the book of Numbers that the
second generation will go into the land.
So, that's what we saw last week. We you
would think at this point that the
people have learned to stop rebelling
and grumbling and complaining against
God, but they haven't. We're going to be
in Numbers chapter 16 today. This is
such an important account for you to
know as a Christian. If you're a
follower of Jesus, you should know this
text because the half brother of Jesus,
Jude, in the New Testament, after Jesus
comes here for us, he writes a book in
the Bible, the book of Jude. And in the
book of Jude, he talks about this right
here. So, he uses the the brother of
Jesus uses this account in scripture to
challenge us to be careful about which
direction we rebel in. That there's
rebellion in us, let's be sure we rebel
in the right direction. So, this is a
famous rebellion that the brother of
Jesus references in the scripture, but
let's see the initial account. This is
Numbers chapter 16 verse 1. Now, Korah,
son of Izhar, son of Kohath, son of Levi
with Dathan and Abiram, son of Eliab and
On, son of Peleth, sons of Reuben. Now,
I want you to notice I have three names
underlined, Korah, Dathan, and Abiram.
These are the three that are going to
form the rebellion, and you see we have
two other names, which would be
ancestors of Korah, Dathan, and and
Abiram. You're going to see in a moment
why I've highlighted them. These are the
tribes that they come from.
So, they took 250 prominent Israelite
men who were leaders of the community
and representatives in the assembly, and
they rebelled against Moses.
They came together against Moses and
Aaron and told them, "You've gone too
far. Everyone in the entire community is
holy and the Lord is among them. Why
then do you exalt yourselves above the
Lord's assembly?"
When Moses heard this, he fell face
down. Then he said to Korah and his
followers, "Tomorrow morning, the Lord
will reveal who belongs to him, who is
set apart, and the one he will let come
near him.
He will let the one he chooses come near
him.
Korah, you and all your followers are to
do this. Take fire pans and tomorrow
place fire in them and put incense on
them before the Lord. Then the man the
Lord chooses will be the one who is set
apart. It is you, Levites, who have gone
too far. This is God's word." Let's stop
here for a moment. Okay, who are these
people and why are they rebelling? There
is Korah and the Levites. They are
rebelling against Aaron, who is the
priest, and that they have a religious
motivation. They're like, "Why is Aaron
the one who gets to be in the presence
of God? We want to be the ones who do
that." And then there's Dathan and
Abiram, and they're rebelling against
Moses because of his civil authority.
"We want to be in the position of
Moses." And so, they are complaining and
grumbling against Moses and Aaron. Now,
some of what they're saying is true.
Which is the problem with grumbling.
Oftentimes there's half-truth mixed with
things that aren't true. It is true that
God had appointed the entire assembly.
It is true that God wanted to appear to
all of the people and show his presence
to people. What was untrue is that Moses
had never put himself in a position
like, "I'm better than you." In fact,
Moses was the reluctant leader who was
constantly saying, "God, if you want
someone else to do this, please put
someone else in charge." But that's
often how grumbling and gossip works.
It's often some things that are true
mixed with things that are not true. And
how did all of these groups come
together? Cuz there's hundreds of
thousands of people in the wilderness.
How do they come together to go against
Moses and Aaron? Well, scholars point
out where they camped.
What do you notice?
What do you notice about the descendants
of Kohath and the descendants of Reuben?
These are all the 12 tribes of Israel
and where they would camp around the
tabernacle. We saw this in our very
first week in the study of the book of
Numbers. You don't have to be a genius
to figure this out.
Complainers unite.
They all camped in the same area.
They grumbled together. This could be
easily for some of you a description of
what your office looks like or your
neighborhood. It's all of the
complainers coming together uniting on
their complaining.
When I was in my young 20s, I was in a
mentoring group with an older pastor and
he was mentoring a group of uh younger
pastors. And there was one guy in the
group who in a group setting, he meant
this as a flex. Like he was kind of
bragging on himself. He was saying,
"Hey, it seems like people always come
to me with their complaints. I think I'm
just a safe person. I think there's
something about me that people just know
they can come to me."
And the older pastor looked at him and
said, "Son,
that's not good.
You should ask what signal you're
sending that everyone thinks they can
come and unite with you around their
complaining and their grumbling. This is
what was happening on the south side of
the tabernacle. This is the complainers
from the south side and they were really
struggling with what Moses and Aaron
that they were the leaders and this
really bothered them. Moses then reminds
them, "Hey, I'm I'm going to sum up the
next section." Reminds them that you're
Levites. You have such an amazing thing
that you get to do. You guard the
tabernacle. But for these people it
wasn't enough. They wanted more.
Remember, this is the group of people
that God had fed manna, bread from
heaven in the wilderness, and the bread
from heaven, the manna, wasn't enough.
They wanted more. And here, they have a
position as being Levites, but it's not
enough. They want more. Moses wants to
meet with them. They won't meet and they
send word to Moses. This is in verse 13.
Is it not enough that you brought us
from a land flowing with milk and honey
to kill us in the wilderness? Do you
also have to appoint yourself as ruler
over us? Okay, this is crazy what they
just said. They said, "You brought us
out of Egypt, a land of milk and honey."
This is how you know that grumbling
makes you foolish. They were rescued
from slavery in Egypt. Now, they are
looking back at their slavery and they
are saying, "That's the land flowing
with milk and honey." The promised land
that God had for his people was the land
that God said is flowing with milk and
honey. This awesome land that God has
for his people. But no, these people,
they've complained themselves and and
grumbled themselves into foolish
thinking where they actually look back
at their slavery and say, "That was the
land filling flowing with milk and
honey." This is so deeply offensive to
God that they long for their old life.
See, grumbling is so illogical and
rebellion is often illogical.
Those 10 inmates that escaped from the
prison in New Orleans that I found
myself rooting for until I read all
about their stories, they they made a
foolish choice when they escaped because
they had no plan. 10 inmates escaped and
within hour several of them were
captured. One the next day sitting on a
park bench. One 2 days later because he
was posting on social media and people
could find where he was located. Within
months all of them were recaptured. And
so their decision to rebel actually cost
them more because now they have
additional time added to their sentence.
It was illogical.
And you know the rebellion that is the
most illogical?
It's our rebellion against God.
I mean, let's just be honest how foolish
we are
when we choose to try and find life in
something other than God.
We are actually telling ourselves, we
are fooling ourselves in the thinking
that some created thing is going to be
able to do more for us than our creator
who gave himself for us. When we rebel
against him, we actually are believing
the lie that something other than him is
going to be enough for us, but it's
always less than him. When we rebel
against him, we are looking at our old
lives and saying our old lives that he
rescued us from is really the land
flowing with milk and honey. It is so
foolish. And so you see again the
foolishness of their grumbling, the
foolishness of their rebellion. And the
very next morning is when there is going
to be the test that Moses subjected them
to. He said, "Listen, here's what we're
going to do. Each person is going to
bring a fire pan." A fire pan is like a
sensor and there's going to be incense
in it. This is how they would enter into
the presence of God in the tabernacle,
but this was supposed to be Aaron that
is doing this. But these people are
saying, "We want Aaron's job. We want
this." And Moses said, "Okay, let's see
what happens if you enter into the
presence of God, though he's not
appointed you to do so. Let's see what
happens. Bring a fire pan, bring some
incense. Let's see who God approves of.
Let's see what happens next. Skip down
to verse 18. This is the very next
morning. Each man took his fire pan,
placed fire in it, so it's a a pan or a
sensor where incense comes out of it,
and put incense on it and stood at the
entrance of the tent of meeting along
with Moses and Aaron. After Korah
assembled the whole community against
them at the entrance to the tent of the
meeting, the glory of the Lord appeared
to the whole community. The Lord spoke
to Moses and Aaron, "Separate yourselves
from this community so I may consume
them instantly."
Okay, this is a shocking text. This is a
very quick rebellion.
These are people who are saying, "We're
going to prove that we can do what Aaron
and Moses do." They they walk in
unauthorized into the tabernacle, and
God says, "I am going to consume them
instantly."
Moses, because he loves these people, he
begged God to be merciful. And so, God
tells Moses, "Tell everyone else in the
community to get away from the tents of
these people. Tell everyone else to get
away." And notice what happens next,
verse 31. Just as he finished speaking
all these words, the ground beneath them
split open. The earth opened its mouth
and swallowed them and their households.
All Korah's people and all their
possessions, they went down alive in the
Sheol, the grave, with all that belonged
to them. The earth closed over them, and
they vanished from the assembly. At
their cries, the people of Israel all
all the people of Israel who were around
them fled because they thought, "The
earth may swallow us, too."
Now, this is God's word, and this is an
intense passage. This is God quickly
stifling, ending the rebellion, and
bringing judgment because he's a holy
God, and these people were not
approaching him in the way that he had
prescribed that they approach him. This
is God's holy judgment. This is not just
some natural sinkhole. I had a sinkhole,
my wife and I had a sinkhole in our
house in Cincinnati. It was in our front
yard and neighbors would kind of make
fun of us like you guys are going to
fall in. Be careful going into your
house. There was ground that just kind
of started getting
just it was sinking down. It was a big
hole in our yard, but it happened over
time and we would just kind of laugh
about it and and go around and go into
our house and eventually got it filled
with dirt and put grass on it and
everything was fine. This is an
instantaneous judgment of God, massive
hole, the people are consumed and the
hole is brought back and all of Israel
who saw it happen flees. This is God
bringing judgment. Now at this point
surely surely the people would stop
complaining against God.
At this point surely they're going to
realize wow, this God is holy and when
he says this is what's going to happen,
this is exactly what's happening. But
flip the page and you'll see in verse 41
the very next day, no way. There's no
way they still complain.
Surely they're going to stop grumbling.
Verse 41.
The next day
the entire Israelite community
complained about Moses and Aaron saying,
"You have killed the Lord's people."
When the community assembled against
them, Moses and Aaron turned toward the
tent of meeting and suddenly the cloud
covered it and the Lord's glory
appeared. Moses and Aaron went to the
front of the tent of the meeting and the
Lord said to Moses, "Get away from this
community so I may consume them
instantly." But they fell face down. God
then sends a plague to these people who
are grumbling and complaining once
again. Moses asked Aaron the priest to
run into the people to offer a sacrifice
to offer incense so that God's anger
will be turned away from these people.
And that's what Aaron does, verse 47.
So, Aaron took his fire pan as Moses had
ordered, ran into the middle of the
assembly, and saw that the plague had
begun among the people. After he had
added incense, he made atonement for the
people. He stood between the dead and
the living, and the plague was halted.
This is God's word. Aaron loved these
people, so he ran into the plague. He
risked his own life, even though these
people didn't want him. He was willing
to run into the depth of the moment and
offer a sacrifice, and offer incense so
that God would smell the offering and
turn his wrath, turn his holy anger away
from that moment. Now, this scene is so
epic. I mean, it is a intense account.
Some people, some modern readers may
struggle with this. Wow, what kind of
God is this that sends judgment like
this? What kind of account is this?
We must understand as we read the whole
scripture that this is really a um
a snapshot of truths that we read about
God in the scripture. We understand that
God is more holy than we ever could
imagine. He is more righteous, more holy
than we could ever fully know.
We love the sun here in Southern
California. It's amazing, but we also
know that the sun must be taken
seriously. That you're not going to just
walk up and approach the sun, that you
would instantly You would instantly die.
The sun is just too powerful, too
awesome. And God's holiness is the same
way. We love that he's holy because he
gives us real life, but we can't just
casually approach the the presence of a
holy God. So, God is more holy than we
imagine, too. We are more sinful than we
often think that we are.
That because God is more holy that our
struggles are more sinful, our
iniquities, are the things that we have
done to rebel against God, we may
sometimes view them as small, we may
view grumbling or complaining as small,
but compared to a holy God, they are,
according to the scripture, utterly
sinful. We are more sinful than we often
imagine ourselves to be. That includes
me. Now, I want to be honest. I've seen
some pastors take this text that I am
teaching to you today and use it to
manipulate people. I've heard pastors
take this text and essentially say, "I'm
Moses. I'm the leader of the community,
and you shouldn't complain against me,
and you should follow whatever direction
that I give." That's a misapplication of
this text. Because in the New Testament,
none of us are Moses. I'm not Moses. In
the New Testament, Jesus is the greater
and better Moses. I'm like you in the
community. I am deeply sinful, just like
you. I need God's grace, just like you.
So, I'm not taking this passage and
saying, "Listen, I'm Moses. You should
follow me wherever I go." I'm not Moses.
Jesus is the better Moses. I, like you,
have fallen woefully short of God's
glory, but in the community, I am
reminding us that God is holy, and that
we have all fallen short.
And therefore, number three, we need a
mediator.
All of us need a mediator. God is more
holy than we can imagine. We are more
sinful than we often realize that we
are, and we need a mediator. Aaron, who
runs into the plague, gives us a picture
of Jesus. We need a mediator. One who's
going to go before God the Father and
have the holy anger against sin turned
from us. Jesus actually accomplishes
more than what Aaron accomplished. Aaron
ran into the plague, and he had God's
wrath just turned away. Jesus ran into
the plague, the brokenness, the
sinfulness of this world, and he didn't
only have that holy anger of God turned
away, but he had it absorbed in his own
flesh. Aaron ran into the death and the
plague, and Jesus stepped into this
world to seek and to save that which is
lost. Aaron risked his life for people
that he loved. Jesus did more than just
risk his life. Jesus the Christ gave his
life for us. Aaron carried a censer into
the plague. Jesus carried the cross, and
as he was placed on the cross, the wrath
of God wasn't just turned, the wrath of
God was absorbed in Jesus for 6 hours as
he was crucified in our place, and he
yelled out, "It is finished." This is
such good news for us. There is no more
wrath for God to pour out on you because
Jesus has absorbed all of it. He drank
the cup of God's wrath to the very last
drop. So, the only thing that is left
for you is the mercy and grace of Jesus,
and his grace is bigger than all of our
sin, including all of the times we've
grumbled and complained. His grace is
bigger.
And there's one thing I want to point
out in the scripture that just reminds
us how awesome his grace is.
Korah
and all the people in his family were
swallowed up, but clearly there's some
of his descendants that actually moved
into the promised land.
And that they actually believed in God's
grace. How do we know? Oh, this is so
fascinating to me. In the scripture,
there's 150 Psalms. Three of them in the
original language are written by the
sons of Korah.
Psalm 52, I'm sorry, Psalm 42, Psalm 46,
and Psalm 84. Psalm 84, the sons of
Korah write, "Better is 1 day in your
house, oh Lord, than a thousand
elsewhere. I would rather be a a
I'd rather watch the tent of God than
dwell in the house of the wicked." The
sons of Korah are saying, "It it doesn't
matter to me if I'm the if I'm on the
outside. I just want to be close to
God's grace. And so they the the
descendants of Korah
understand the power and the grace and
the glory of our great God, that His
grace is big. So here is the lesson that
you must walk away from this text. Jude,
the half-brother of Jesus, tells this
account in the book of Jude. He says,
"Don't be like the sons of Korah. The
sons of Korah rebelled against the grace
of God." The reason Jude wrote that, it
was 30 or 40 years after Jesus was
resurrected from the dead. There's a
whole bunch of people becoming
Christians. Then some of the people
who'd become Christians started saying,
"I'm not sure I want to become I'm not
sure I want Jesus." I and they started
to walk away. Just like the people in
the wilderness started saying, "I don't
know if God's grace is really awesome. I
want to go back to Egypt." And so Jude
said, "Whatever you do, don't be like
the sons
of Korah. Don't be like Korah. Don't
rebel this way."
You're going to rebel, but rebel in the
right way.
Rebel against grumbling, not against His
grace. There's something in with all of
us that we just we're going to rebel.
So ask God to purify your rebellion. If
you give Him your heart, if you worship
God in all of what He's done for you,
because Christ ran into your plague and
removed all of your sin and your shame,
if you're in all of Him, you want to
give Him your heart, and then you want
to rebel
against your grumbling.
You want to rebel in the right way.
Grumbling spread in the account in the
book of Numbers. It spread on the south
side of the tabernacle, and grumbling
still spreads. Grumbling spreads, and
grumbling will spread in your heart and
my heart. Grumbling will spread in our
hearts and cause us to be frustrated and
filled with anxiousness and anger, and
grumbling will spread in our minds
causing us to be illogical and foolish,
actually viewing our former lives as the
lives that would have milk and honey.
Grumbling spreads in you. And so, what
you have to do is rebel against
grumbling. Don't rebel against his
grace. Rebel against your grumbling.
How do you rebel against your grumbling?
Well, you see the grumbling start to
spread in your life and you're like, I
don't want this to happen at all to me.
Grumbling is going to be a temptation
for you. Why? Because you're in the
wilderness and life in the wilderness is
often challenging. And because you're
human, just like I'm human, there's
going to be moments when you are tempted
to grumble. You live in a culture
surrounded by grumbling. You're going to
be tempted to grumble. So, rebel against
your grumbling.
If you find yourself on social media
constantly going down a rabbit hole that
causes you to see news that just
frustrates you, rebel against your
grumbling by spending less time on
social media.
If while you're on social media, you you
see accounts of other people and it
causes you to be filled with envy or
angry towards them, rebel against your
grumbling by spending less time on that
app.
If
you find yourself with a group of people
and this group of people, you just see
it when you're with them, the worst
parts of you get pulled out. Their
grumbling inspires your grumbling and
you're just like the people on the south
side of the tabernacle, your grumbling
when you're with them just multiplies,
well, limit your time with this group of
people.
Rebel against your grumbling. Be angry
at your grumbling.
If you find that on Sunday evenings you
start looking at what your week looks
like and you start to grumble against
your job. You don't like your boss and
you don't like the mission of the
organization. You don't like the team
that you're working on. You share with
your spouse or with a friend every
Sunday night. You're looking at the
calendar and you're like,
and your grumbling starts to increase.
What do you do in that moment? You rebel
against your grumbling by reminding
yourself how awesome God has been to
you. That he's providing for you. That
the job you have is a provision from
God. That he's rescued you. That he's
pulled you out of slavery and out of all
of your sin and all of your shame. You
rebel against your grumbling by
remembering his grace. You rebel against
your grumbling by asking God to increase
your awe for his grace in your life.
That he is Jesus the Christ is the
mediator who ran into
the darkness, the sinfulness of this
world.
And on the cross, he absorbed in his
flesh all of your sin and your shame and
all of the punishment that should have
been mine, he absorbed. All of the
punishment that should have been yours,
he absorbed. Why would we rebel against
his grace? Why would we rebel against
him? The one who can satisfy the
longings of our souls unlike anything or
anyone else. Why would we rebel against
him? No, you be wise this week. You
don't rebel against his grace. You rebel
against your grumbling. So, get angry at
your grumbling. Decide right now, "No,
I'm not going out like that. I'm not
going to be like Korah. I'm not doing
this. No way." And so, you fill your
heart with gratitude for God's grace in
your life. You don't surround yourself
with people that are going to pull you
into grumbling. You don't throw yourself
into environments that it's going to
pull your grumbling to the surface
because when you do, you bring
anxiousness into your heart and
foolishness into your mind. No, get
ticked off at your grumbling and fight
against it. Rebel against your
grumbling. Don't rebel against his
grace. Receive his grace and rebel
against your grumbling.
Hey, I'm so glad that you joined us for
[music] our service today. And I hope
and pray that God use this message to
encourage you right where you are.
I'd love if you hit the subscribe button
>> [music]
>> cuz then you can get the next alert for
whenever we have services and when that
we ever offer content here on [music]
YouTube. So subscribe and join us for
Mariners online.